打了保龄球 泡了吧以后
After balling, I go clubbing
拥抱过之后
Then I’m hugging
我肚子又饿了 我走在街上
Then I’m hungry and I’m walking on the street
开始变得暴躁
And I’m getting getting getting getting grumpy grumpy
就在这时 我的右边
I see Chow, by my right
我闻到了食物的味道
I smell food in the air
是中国菜 我的最爱
It’s Chinese Food, my favorite
我要饿疯了
So I’m getting getting getting getting hungry
我爱中国菜
I love Chinese food (Yeah)
你知道这是真的
You know that it’s true (Yeah)
我爱炒饭
I love fried rice (Yeah)
我爱面条
I love noodles (Yeah)
我爱炒面
I love Chow mein
炒面面面面面
Chow Mo-Mo-Mo-Mo Mein
我爱中国菜
I love Chinese food (Yeah)
你知道这是真的
You know that it’s true (Yeah)
我爱炒饭
I love fried rice (Yeah)
我爱面条
I love noodles (Yeah)
我爱炒面
I love Chow mein
炒面面面面面
Chow Mo-Mo-Mo-Mo Mein
看看菜单
Read the menu
他们有西兰花
They got broccoli
还有鸡翅
Even chicken wings
是香辣味的
Make it spicy
你会喜欢上的
And you like it
因为太漂亮了
Cause it’s beautiful
而且味道好~极~了~
And it tastes so so so good
我喜欢鸡蛋卷
I like their egg rolls
还有混沌汤
And their wonton soup
让我觉得太棒了
This makes me feel so so good
幸运饼干 预告我未来
Fortune cookies, tell my future
中国~中国菜
Chinese Chinese Food
我爱中国菜
I love Chinese food (Yeah)
你知道这是真的
You know that it’s true (Yeah)
我爱炒饭
I love fried rice (Yeah)
我爱面条
I love noodles (Yeah)
我爱炒面
I love Chow mein
炒面面面面面
Chow Mo-Mo-Mo-Mo Mein
我爱中国菜
I love Chinese food (Yeah)
你知道这是真的
You know that it’s true (Yeah)
我爱炒饭
I love fried rice (Yeah)
我爱面条
I love noodles (Yeah)
我爱炒面
I love Chow mein
炒面面面面面
Chow Mo-Mo-Mo-Mo Mein
Patrice Wilson：：哟！
Patrice Wilson：Yo!
我喜欢中国菜
I like Chinese food
还有混沌汤
And some Wonton soup
给我西兰花
Get me broccoli
当我玩《大富翁》（桌面游戏）
While I play Monopoly
别手忙脚乱
Don’t be a busy bee
这是你的梦想
Cause it’s your fantasy
去品尝中国菜
To eat Chinese food
鸡蛋卷和大杂烩
Egg roll and Chop Suey
我用筷子
I use the chopsticks
在锅里夹菜
To eat pot sticks
放一些辣酱让食物更美味
Put some hot sauce and sweet and sour make it sweet
因为中国菜 让我更轻松自在
Because Chinese food takes away my stress
现在我要去熊猫快餐（中式餐馆）
Now I’m going to go eat Panda Express
我爱中国菜
I love Chinese food (Yeah)
你知道这是真的
You know that it’s true (Yeah)
我爱炒饭
I love fried rice (Yeah)
我爱面条
I love noodles (Yeah)
我爱炒面
I love Chow mein
炒面面面面面
Chow Mo-Mo-Mo-Mo Mein
我爱中国菜
I love Chinese food (Yeah)
你知道这是真的
You know that it’s true (Yeah)
我爱炒饭
I love fried rice (Yeah)
我爱面条
I love noodles (Yeah)
我爱炒面
I love Chow mein
炒面面面面面
Chow Mo-Mo-Mo-Mo Mein
翻译：94爱可
幸运饼干永远不会犯错